Guide to the Joseph Veverka papers, 1942-2013,
Veverka, Joseph papers,
- Series IV. Mission Files
  - Sample Return and Flybys, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - P. Landecker: TRW/Cornell, 2002-05-2002-07 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Vespir/New World Explorer Proposal Binzel/Veverka, 2000-06-2000-12 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Venus, 2007-10 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - APL 6/11/03, 2003-06-11 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - 8-12 to 8-15 Joe BWI, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - April 4-11, 2003 Meeting JPL, Boulder, CO, 2003-04-04-2003-04-11 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - JPL DocuShare Instructions, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - NNO Workshop JPL, Pasada, CA Joe, 2003-08-27-2003-08-29 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - 6/4/03 Honeybee Robotics NYC - Joe CSSR, 2003-06-04 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Discovery C4, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Proprietary and Competition Sensitive Information
  - Discovery Program report, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Comet Hopper (Chopper), 2009-01 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Proprietary Information
  - APL Nereus June, 2005-06 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Contains Competition Sensitive Information
  - C-G Impactor, 2008-09 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Comet Odyssey, 2008-01-2008-02 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Competition Sensitive Information
  - NASA Epoch, 2006-04 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Constitutes a "trade secret and/or information that is commercial or financial and confidential or privilaged"
  - Orbital Technical Interchange Meeting, 2008-03 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Notes and Asteroid Pictures, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Unlabeled Asteroid Pictures, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled Asteroid and Space Pictures, Undated (Box 28)
  - Asteroid Sample Return Cost Preview, 2008-09-16 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    JPL/APL Competition Sensitive Information
  - Integrated Characterization of Europa: The Search for an Ocean, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Titan and Enceladus Feasibility Study Report, 2007-01-30 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - International Mars Architecture for the Return of Samples (iMARS) Report, 2008-06-01 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Comet Hopper DSMCE Study Mid-Term Review, 2008-11-19 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Stardust-NExT
    - Stardust-NExT, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Stardust next flyby, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - 1/19/11 DC: Stardust-NExT, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Tempel 1/Stardust, 2010-2011 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - StardustNExT Tempel 1, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - StardustNExT Tempel 1 articles and press kit, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Stardust NExT Appendix 12, 2009-01-29 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Stardust-NExT Results, 2011-12-15 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Tempel 1 Encounter Console Procedure, 2011-02-09 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - STARDUST-NExT, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - STARDUST-NExT, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Stardust NExT, 2006-2011 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Stardust-NExT, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Stardust-NExT, 2007-2011 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Stardust-NExT, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Stardust NExT Results, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Stardust NExT Results, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Stardust NEXT, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Stardust NEXT, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Stardust NExT, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Stardust-NExT, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      Proprietary and Export Controlled Information
    - Tempel 1 Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - EPOXI / Stardust NExT Notes, 2006-2011 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Stardust NExT, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Stardust NExT, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cassini
    - Cassini, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Cassini, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Cassini, 2001-12-2004 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Cassini, 1987-1991 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      2 notebooks
  - Comet Surface Sample Return (CSSR)
    - CSSR Mission Proposals, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Comet Surface Sample Return (CSSR) Mission Proposal Disk 1 of 2, 2004-02-13; CD-5026 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      New frontiers AO 03-OSS-03
    - Comet Clipper Mission Proposal, 2004-02-13; CD-5027 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Comet Surface Sample Return (CSSR) Mission Proposal disk 2 of 2, 2004-02-13; CD-5028 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - 28-29 Oct JPL CSSR, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - 10-28-02, JPL, 2nd mtg CSSR, 2002-10-28 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - 8-11 Sep Joe CSSR JPL, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - 9-9-02, JPL, 1st mtg CSSR, 2002-09 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - CSSR List Serve, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - JPL Travel March 13-14, 2003 CSSR, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Comet Clipper Proposal, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Comet Clipper Memorandum of Understanding (MOU), 2004-01-27 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - CSSR Memorandum of Understanding (MOU), 2003 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - NASA Cover Page and Notice of Intent (NOI) Comet Clipper, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Resumes for Comet Clipper Proposal, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - CSSR Science Team Bios and Roles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - CSSR Planetary Protection, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - 5/22 Telecon CSSR, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - CSSR Telecon 5/8/04, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - CSSR: Oct 22/23 JPL, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - CSSR 10/22 - 10/23/03 JPL Joe, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Comet Surface Sample Return (CSSR) Mission Study, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      Contains Competition Sensitive and Lockheed Martin Proprietary Information
    - CSSR Science Working Group, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - 3-13-03, JPL 3rd Meeting CSSR, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      Proprietary, Competition Sensitive, and Company Confidential Information
    - Comet Sample Return!, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - CSSR Proposal Guidelines, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - CSSR, Deep Space Observatories, 2004-2008 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      Competition Sensitive and Proprietary Information
    - CSSR Proposal Authorization Review, 2003-11-04 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Competition Sensitive
    - June 19-19, 2003 Meeting LhM, Denver CO CSSR, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Competition Sensitive, Proprietary, and Discreet Information
    - Mission and Science Reviews CSSR, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - CSSR, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - CSSR Folder 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Contains Competition Sensitive and Proprietary Information
    - CSSR Folder 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Contains Proprietary information
    - CSSR Notes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - CSSR, Undated (Box 29, Folder 46)
      Contains Proprietary/Competition Sensitive Information
  - Rendezvous with a Comet Nucleus (RECON)
    - RECON(Rendezvous with a Comet Nucleus), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Comet Nucleus Tour (CONTOUR)
    - The Comet Nucleus Tour (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - The Comet Nucleus Tour (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - CONTOUR, MARDI, MARC1, MGS, 1988-2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - CONTOUR 1999, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - CONTOUR Presentation, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - CONTOUR/ CONTOUR Launch, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - CONTOUR 2001, articles, correspondence, launch and flight info, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - CONTOUR Slides, 1950-2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Includes A Comet Model. I. The Acceleration of Comet Encke by Fred Whipple
    - CONTOUR Presentation, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - CONTOUR Launch, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Deep Impact
    - Scarquest, 2003-2006 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Crash Course Article/Deep Impact, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Deep Impact Encounter with Comet 9p, 2005-07-04 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Discovery Proposals Deep Impact, 1998-06-1999-07 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Scarquest, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - EPOXI and Deep Impact Posters and Presentations, 2005-2008 (Box 28)
  - Mars Exploration Program NASA
    - Mars Orbital Camera (MOC), 2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Includes photographs and slides
    - MARCI, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - MARDI, 1998-09-1999-12 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Mars Global Surveyor, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Mars Exploration Rover Mission Info, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Near Earth Asteroid Rendezvous (NEAR)
    - NEAR, 1991-1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - NEAR, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Near Earth Object Detection, 1992-01 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - NEAR Slides (Folder 1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      includes photographs and slides
    - NEAR Slides (Folder 2 of 3), Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - NEAR, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      includes photographs
    - NEAR Slides (Folder 3 of 3), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - NEAR at Eros, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Slides about asteroids and NEAR, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Near Earth Object Spacecraft Study, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - NEAR, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Discovery #1: NEAR, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Discovery Missions to Near Earth Objects, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Discovery: NEAR, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - NEAR Eros, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - NEAR Correspondence and Images, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - NEAR 253 Mathilde, Undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - NEAR LAF ms., Undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - NEAR: NASA HQ, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Includes Photographs
    - NEAR 1999 Folder 1 of 2, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - NEAR 1999 Folder 2 of 2, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - NEAR 1995 II Folder 1 of 2, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - NEAR 1995 II Folder 2 of 2, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - NEAR Proposals Vol. II Management and Cost Plans, 1994-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - NEAR Eros Flyby, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - NEAR Proposals Vol. I Investigation and Technical Plan, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Mathilda Flyby, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Mathilde Encounter NEAR Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - NEAR - 2000 Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - NEAR Poster, Undated (Box mapcase, Folder 1)
  - Galileo
    - Galileo at Jupiter, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Contains slides
    - Galileo, 1990-1997 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      includes slides
    - Galileo, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - HIIPS, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - NIMS, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Galileo Status Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Galileo - Software, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - GLL - Image Processing - General, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Galileo - Project Policy, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Galileo Supv, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - VEEGA Trajectory, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Asteroid Policy - Notes/Policies, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Amphitrite Encounter - Recommendations, 1985-09 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Summery - Working Group Rec. Galileo Asteroid Flyby, 1984-12-06 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - ESA/NASA Primitive Bodies Science Study Group Galileo Asteroid Flyby, 1984-12-13 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - HIIPS, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Galileo Lunar Science Workshop, 1992-07-31 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Galileo, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Galileo SDPG Meeting, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - GLL SPICE Workshop, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) Galileo Internal Memorandum, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Cornell HIIPS Status, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Galileo Software Interface Specification, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Multimission Image Processing, 1995-04-19 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Computer program module thhTest.c, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Galileo SSI Unprocesed Data Record (UDR) for Optical Navigation (OPNAV), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Galileo SSI Image Catalog (Jupiter Encounter), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Galileo SSI Image Catalog for phase II (Jupiter Encounter), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Galileo SSI Raw Experiment Data Record (REDR), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - MIPS Galileo Tutorial Overview, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Integrated Software for Imaging Spectometers (ISIS), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Jupiter Imaging Science Subsystem EDR images, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Vicar Workshop, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Galileo Spice Event Kernel, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Rayshade, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Galileo Imaging Science team Meeting #75, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Press Release and News articles regarding Europa, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Galileo Solid State Imaging (SSI) Prime Mission Final Report, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - GLL SSI SDPG Meeting - BTC, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - JPL Minutes of Galileo Imaging Science Team Meeting #73, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - JPL Minutes of the SSI Team Meeting, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - JPL Minutes of the 71st SSI Team Meeting, Tucson, AZ, 1997-04-17-1997-04-18 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - JPL Minutes of SSI Team Meeting #70, 1997-03-28 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - JPL Minutes of Galileo Imaging Science Team Meeting #69, 1997-01-09 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - JPL Minutes of Galileo Imaging Science Team #68, 1996-10-22 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - JPL Galileo Imaging Science Team meeting #67 minutes, 1996-09-23 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - JPL Galileo Imaging Science Team Meeting #66 minutes, 1996-06-24 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - JPL Minutes of Galileo Imaging Science Team Meeting #65, 1996-03-26 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - JPL Minutes of SSI Team Meeting #64, 1995-11-09 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - JPL Minutes of the SSI Team Meeting #63, 1995-10-02 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - JPL Minutes of SSI Team Meeting #62 Galileo, 1995-05-30 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Multi-mission Image Processing Laboratory (MIPL) Failure Report History, 1991-05-21 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - CAMMTFS, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - JPL Data Management Section Multimission Image Processing System, 1994-11-28 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Version 1.4
    - JPL Data Management Section Multimission Image Processing System, 1995-05-10 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Version 1.5
    - JPL Data Management Section Multimission Image Processing System, 1995-06-10 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Version 1.2
    - Images of the Venus Cloud Deck from Galileo, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - JOP/Galileo Science Group Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - JOP/Galileo Imaging Sub-Groups - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - JOP - Letters, Reports 1977, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Galileo - Letters/Reports 1978, 1974-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Galileo - Letters, Reports 1979, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Satellite News, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Proposals - JOP, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Jovian Atmosphere Science Reports, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Jupiter Sequencing Expectations, Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Galileo Imaging Team Filter Situation, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Satellite/rings working group, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Galileo, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Galileo Preliminary Trajectory Characteristics, 1977-12 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Galileo Project Science Management Plan, 1978-01-17 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Galileo Project Science Management Plan, 1978-01-17 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Galileo Program Objectives and Descriptions of tentatively Selected Investigations, 1978-05-05 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Galileo Reference Mission Trajectory Characteristics, 1978-08-17 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Galileo Policies and Requirements for Orbiter Science Investigations, 1978-04-05 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Project Galileo Reference Mission Trajectory Characteristics, 1979-05-11 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Galileo Solid State Imaging (SSI) Preliminary Design Review, 1979-08-28 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Galileo Atmospheric Structure in the Equatorial Region of Jupiter, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Galileo Review Plan, 1980-09-25 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Galileo Saturn and Tempel II Missions, 1982-12-10 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Galileo Design Requirements and Philosophy, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Galileo Mission Requirements Document, 1982-07 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Galileo Policies and Requirements for Orbiter Science Investigations, 1980-05 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Galileo SSI Radiometric Analysis: Part I - Sensor Screening and Engineering Model, 1983-10-04 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Galileo Anomalies in the 2 1/3 Second Frame Rate Raw Data, 1983-09-06 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Galileo Residual Image Analysis, 1983-09-09 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Galileo Limits on SSI Radiometric Precision, 1980-07-12 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Galileo T-Number and Transmission Test Results of the SSI Engineering Model Optics, 1982-06-23 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Galileo EM Calibration - Noise Analysis, 1983-05-23 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Galileo Exposure Optimization for Photometric Accuracy, 1982-10-04 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Galileo EM Calibration - MTF Analysis, 1983-05-17 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Galileo Summary of SSI Low-Light-Level Imaging Sequence Plans, 1983-03-21 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Galileo Mission Plan, Undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
      Volume 1
    - Galileo Mission Plan, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
      Volume 4
    - Galileo NASA End-to-End Data System (NEEDS) Letter, 1981-06-10 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Imaging Defects in Flight SSI, 1981-06-02 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Barc Data Compression for Galileo Imaging, 1979-03-15 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Effects of Data Compression of Cloud Mition Measurement in Planetary Images, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - NEEDS Data Compression Processing as Applied to Photometric Applications Galileo, 1980-09-30 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Study to Determine Effectiveness of BARC decompression software, 1983-09-01 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Galileo Mission Requirements Document, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - STS/Galileo/ISPM Launch Policyu, 1983-03 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - SSI Mark-Up, 1982-02-25 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Composite SSI Camera Profile Galileo, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      Drawing of Camera Design
    - Solid State Imaging (SSI) Instrument Calibration Requirements Documents, 1982-06-11 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Galileo Imaging Science Group Minutes 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Galileo Imaging Science Team Minutes 1982-1983, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Galileo Imaging Science Team Minutes 1984-1985, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Galileo Imaging Science Team Minutes 1986 Folder 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Galileo Imaging Science Team Minutes 1986 Folder 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Galileo Imaging - Hardware Sub-Group/Minutes 1980 - 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Galileo Imaging - Hardware Sub-Group/Minutes 1981-1984, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Galileo Science Requirements and Operations Planning (SROP)/Sub-Group Minutes Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Galileo Science Requirements and Operations Planning (SROP)/Sub-Group Minutes Folder 2 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Remote Sensing Science Group- Minutes Galileo, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Project Steering Group (PSG) - Minutes Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Project Steering Group (PSG) - Minutes Folder 2 of 2, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Project Steering Group (PSG) - Minutes 1984-85, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Project Steering Group (PSG) - Minutes 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Galileo Scientific Data Processing Group/incc. Interim Reports - HIIPS - Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Data Processing Sub-Group - Minutes (HIIPS), 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Galileo Letters and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Galileo Letters and Reports Folder 1 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Galileo Letters and Reports Folder 2 of 2, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Galileo SROP Minutes of Nov. 18-19 meeting, 1985-11-27 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Galileo Science Requirements Document, 1986-11-21 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Ververka Group Galileo, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Galileo Science in the Jovian System, 1982-08-16 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - IDA: Data Lists, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Galileo and Asteroid 243 IDA papers folder 1 of 2, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Galileo and Asteroid 243 IDA papers folder 2 of 2, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Photos taken by Galileo, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Galileo Gaspra encounter, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - SPUD, 1986-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Scientific Data Processing Group (SDPG) Notes and Minutes Folder 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Scientific Data Processing Group (SDPG) Notes and Minutes Folder 2 of 2, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - SSI - Filters - Tests Recommendations, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - SSI - Camera Calibrations/Problems, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Jupiter's Atmosphere - Observation/Tracking Science Reports etc. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Galileo Satellite Tours (Interim) Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Galileo Satellite Tours (Interim) Folder 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Galileo Satellite Tours (Interim) (85-07 to 85-12) Folder 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Galileo Satellite Tours (Interim) (85-07 to 85-12) Folder 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Galileo Jupiter Satellites Trajectory Listings Folder 1 of 3, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Galileo Jupiter Satellites Trajectory Listings Folder 2 of 3, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      Contains Strawman Jupiter Approach Orbit Activity Plan, Orbit Planning Guide
    - Galileo Jupiter Satellites Trajectory Listings Folder 3 of 3, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Contains S/C Views - Jupiter
    - Galileo 2000, 1999-11-2000-11 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Galileo 1999, 1999-01 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Europa, Callisto, etc, 1997-01-1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Galoleo Press Conference, 1998-09-1998-10 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Halley observation opportunity, 1982-02-27 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - CONTOUR II (2) (New)
    - CONTOUR 2, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Notice of Intent (NOI) New CONTOUR, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bios/Roles New CONTOUR, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Cornell contract New CONTOUR, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - New CONTOUR, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - CONTOUR II, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - CONTOUR 2, Undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Contour-2 Options, Bob Farquhar 6/23/03, 2003-06-23 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - New CONTOUR Team members, 2004-05-13 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - New CONTOUR NASA's Decision - Concerns, 2005-06-06 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - New CONTOUR Proposal Final Report and rejection, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - CONTOUR Telecon, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      Proprietary Information, For Official Use Only (FOUO)
  - Cornell Caltech Atacama Telescope (CCAT)
    - Atacama Telescope CCAT Science and Facility Requirements, 2005-07-13 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Caltech Atacama Telescope (CCAT) Feasibility Concept Study, 2005-07-13-2005-07-14 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Caltech Atacama Telescope (CCAT), 2005-07 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Decedal Survey
    - Decadal Survey for Planetary Science 2013-2022, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Vision and Voyages for Planetary Science in the Decade 2013-2022, 2011; CD-5011 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Vision and Voyages for Planetary Science in the Decade 2013-2022, 2011; CD-5012 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Vision and Voyages for Planetary Science in the Decade 2013-2022, 2011; CD-5013 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Vision and Voyages for Planetary Science in the Decade 2013-2022, 2011; CD-5014 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Vision and Voyages for Planetary Science in the Decade 2013-2022, 2011; CD-5015 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Planetary Science Decadal Survey 2009 - White Papers, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Planetary Science Decadal Survey 2009 - White Papers, 2009; DVD-3337 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Canadian Space Agency, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Decadal, 2009-2010 (Box 23, Folder 12)